http://www.kisscafe.com.au/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
We know that your privacy is important to you, so that means your privacy is important to us as well.You can read the full details of our privacy policy below. As a quick summary:We only ask for personal information that we need.We will tell you what information we have recorded about you.If you want any personal information changed or deleted, just ask.WHO WE AREThis is the web site of KISS Cafe.WHAT WE KNOW ABOUT YOUWhen you visit our Web site, our Web server automatically records some general information about your visit, but does not recognise or record any individual information about you. The information we record and use for statistical purposes is:Your server addressThe date and timeThe pages accessed and documents downloadedThe type of browser usedWe can only identify you personally if you give us this information voluntarily.YOUR E-MAIL ADDRESSWe do not know your e-mail address unless you give it to us. We will only record your e-mail address if you send us a message. We will use it only for the purpose for which you have provided it. We will not disclose it without your consent.If you have given us your e-mail address, but do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by unsubscribing or sending us an e-mail via our contact form.HOW WE USE THIS INFORMATIONWe use this information to improve the content of our Web site and analyse what pages people visit, and (if you subscribe to our e-mail newsletters) to keep in touch with you about updates to our Web site. If you use our services, we also use your information to customise the content of our Web site for you.If you supply us with your e-mail address or postal address when requesting a service, we might send you information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending us an e-mail.If you supply your telephone number when ordering a product or service, we will only use it with respect to that order.WHO HAS ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION?We use this information internally and share it with other people or organisations who need to know it as part of working with us in our normal business activities.We do not share your personal information with others except under these conditions, and we do not disclose or sell your personal information for use in mailing lists or databases.FUTURE VARIATIONSFrom time to time, we may use your information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.CORRECTIONSUpon request, we'll tell you what information we have recorded about you. If any of this information is incorrect, or you want us to remove all information about you, please send us an e-mail using our contact form.If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy,  please contact us.MORE INFORMATIONIf you would like to know more about on-line privacy, visit The Australian Privacy Commissioner's web site.
Privacy Policy
(C) Copyright Kiss Cafe 2020
Site powered by emanation
Home
Menu
Book
Opportunity
Contact
